{
  "name": "NFL Trivia",
  "description": "Think you know the NFL? Prove it with this short quiz!",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "Which team was the first Super Bowl champion?",
      "options": [
        "New York Giants",
        "Kansas City Chiefs",
        "Green Bay Packers",
        "Chicago Bears"
      ],
      "answer": "Green Bay Packers"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Who (head) coached the Miami Dolphins to the first undefeated season in NFL history?",
      "options": [
        "George Wilson",
        "Don Shula",
        "Joe Philbin",
        "Jimmy Johnson"
      ],
      "answer": "Don Shula"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the only player on this list not in the Pro Football Hall of Fame.",
      "options": [
        "Marshall Faulk",
        "Marvin Harrison",
        "Marcus Allen",
        "Jerome Bettis"
      ],
      "answer": "Marvin Harrison"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Who is the NFL's career passing yards leader?",
      "options": [
        "Peyton Manning",
        "Brett Favre",
        "Dan Marino",
        "Tom Brady"
      ],
      "answer": "Peyton Manning"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Who holds the NFL's single-season sack record?",
      "options": [
        "Jared Allen",
        "Reggie White",
        "Michael Strahan",
        "Bruce Smith"
      ],
      "answer": "Michael Strahan"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "The team now known as the Indianapolis Colts was previously known as...",
      "options": [
        "Baltimore Ravens",
        "Cleveland Browns",
        "Baltimore Colts",
        "Baltimore Orioles"
      ],
      "answer": "Baltimore Colts"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Which city has never hosted an NFL team?",
      "options": [
        "Honolulu, Hawai'i",
        "Los Angeles, California",
        "Canton, Ohio",
        "Anaheim, California"
      ],
      "answer": "Honolulu, Hawai'i"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Who is the all-time career leader in interceptions?",
      "options": [
        "Charles Woodson",
        "Paul Krause",
        "Night Train Lane",
        "Rod Woodson"
      ],
      "answer": "Paul Krause"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the team that does not currently have a principal owner.",
      "options": [
        "Green Bay Packers",
        "Oakland Raiders",
        "Pittsburgh Steelers",
        "New York Giants"
      ],
      "answer": "Green Bay Packers"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What year was the term \"Super Bowl\" first used to describe the NFL Championship Game?",
      "options": [
        "Super Bowl I - 1967",
        "Super Bowl II - 1968",
        "Super Bowl III - 1969",
        "Super Bowl IV - 1970"
      ],
      "answer": "Super Bowl III - 1969"
    }
  ]
}
